#### **Aarclaine Phanta**

+62-878-8878-6183 | aarclainephanta1@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/aarclaine

## **Summary**

I'm a undergraduate Information Technology from President University. Highly motivated and passionate with a burning passion for Web Development. I have a strong understanding in both front-end and backend programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and MySQL. I have experience in 3D Design and Game Development.

I also have a track record of successfully coordinating and leading diverse teams. Currently, I hold a leadership role in the Spirituality Division at Keluarga Mahasiswa Buddhist Ashokavardhana President University.

#### **Education**

#### President University - Cikarang, Indonesia

Aug 2021 - Present

Bachelor of Information Technology

- Cumulative GPA: 3.48 / 4.0
- Relevant Coursework: 3D Computer Graphics and Animation; Artificial intelligence; Computer Network; Network Security; Object Oriented and Visual Programming; Database; Game Development; Internet of Things

# Experience

## Keluarga Mahasiswa Buddhist Ashokavardhana - Cikarang, Indonesia

# Head of Spirituality

Dec 2022 - Present

- Leading a team of 5 members.
- Manage Spiritual activities, worships, and Outing activities on weekly and monthly basis.

### Supervisor of Farewell Day 2023

May 2023 - July 2023

- Organize, educate, and assisting 28 Committees, ensuring seamless execution of the event
- Monitored and Evaluated every performance of each committee
- Conducted 3 Regular Meetings for Progress Report, and giving advice for each committee

### Member of Documentation and Design

June 2022 - Sep 2022

- Designed the logo for the event
- Designed Paid Promote and questionnaire services for IG Stories and post
- Designed coming soon post for the event
- Designed certificate for comitee

### Bekasi Stray Cat's Care

June 2022 - Aug 2022

- Supported the social project as event organizer
- providing schedules and plans for 2 days event
- Opened a donation for stray cat care

# **Projects**

#### 3D 2B Model Animation

- Utilize Blender Feature for creating model such as Sculpting, Compositing, Shading, Animating, Texture
- Highest Score in the class with 95.7/100

#### WhatsDown

- Web Application made with PHP
- implemented CRUD operations in SQL for efficient data management
- Made UI for chat using PHP, and CSS

#### Smart Weather IOT | Group Project as member

- IOT Project with Arduino Uno
- using LDR, DHT-11, and Rain sensor as input system
- using Buzzer and LCD as Output System
- This project comes with Android App for tracking and triggering alarm using BLYNK

#### Horror Hospital game | Group Project as Leader

- 3D Horror game with Unity
- Create and Designed large scaled map and composite the whole map, object and texture
- Using Alternative way to interact with item using reach tool instead of RayCasting
- Made a script for player movement, interaction, lighting, etc
- Making animation for opening a door, chest and lock

# Additional

- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript, C, C++, C#, Java, UI/UX, VSCode, Python, Firebase, MySQL, Blender, Figma, Canve, PhpMyAdmin
- Soft skills: Leadership, Decision Making, Fast Learning, Communication, Attention to detail, Problem Solving, Teamwork
- Languanges: Proficient in English, Native in Indonesia